oreck.com 2015-06-23

# Oreck Privacy Policy

At Oreck Corporation, we respect the privacy of your information. We provide this explanation about our online information practices as a show of our commitment to protect your privacy.

## The Information We Collect

At the time you make a purchase request, we collect and store your name, address, credit card numbers and other personally-identifying information. We need this information to provide and to authorize our retail partners and service providers to provide goods and services that you request and to let you know of additional goods and services about which you might be interested. We also use this information to customize your experience using our Website.

We may ask you for personally-identifying information at other times, such as if you enter into a promotion, communicate with us, or complete a survey. If you opt-in to receive information regarding a promotion, you give us your permission to share your name and e-mail address with the third party offering the promotion.

In addition, we automatically gather general non-personal, statistical information about our Website and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, etc., but in doing so we do not reference you by individual name, e-mail address, home address, or telephone number. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how much our customers use parts of our site so we can improve our site. We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission. We may also match user information we collect with offline data available from other sources in order to carry out our services and conduct target advertising and promotions more effectively.

## Cookies

At Oreck.com, we use a technology called "cookies" on our website. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to make your visit to our website easier. For example, cookies allow us to recognize you when you re-enter our website so that you will not have to sign-in each time you visit. Cookies also allow us to count the number of unique and return visitors who use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser to notify you when you've received a cookie or, alternatively, to refuse to accept cookies. It is important to note that you may not be able to use certain features on our website if you choose not to accept cookies, such as . In addition, you will not be able to participate in any of our sweepstakes or contests.

From time to time, third-party research companies may set cookies on your browser to track exposure to certain ad placements. These cookies may be used for research purposes if you later opt-in to take a survey. If you choose to take the survey, these companies may examine your browser to see if one of their cookies has been set. If the company detects the cookie in your browser, it will gather only 2 pieces of information from it: where you have seen a particular ad and how many times you have seen it. If you do not want these kinds of cookies to be set to your browser, you can opt-out by clicking here. We do not set these kinds of cookies on your browser.

## Third Party Practices

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our site may differ from ours.

From time to time, third-party research companies may set cookies on your browser to track exposure to certain ad placements. These cookies may be used for research purposes if you later opt-in to take a survey. If you choose to take the survey, these companies may examine your browser to see if one of their cookies has been set. If the company detects the cookie in your browser, it will gather only 2 pieces of information from it: where you have seen a particular ad and how many times you have seen it. If you do not want these kinds of cookies to be set to your browser, you can opt-out by [clicking here](http://ch.questionmarket.com/site/subnav/optout.html). We do not set these kinds of cookies on your browser.

At Oreck, we use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on other websites. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and Clear Gif technology (aka 1x1 Pixel .gifs, Web bugs) to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Website and other Websites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, the cookie they used, and your IP address. It may also contain your personally identifiable information if that is something you have agreed to with the applicable third party. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. Advertiser does not use or have access to this information.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting or reading cookies on your computer, you may either visit each ad network's website individually and opt out or visit the website of the National Advertising Initiative ("NAI") to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click here for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies' privacy policies.

To opt-out of third party tracking please click here: [clicking here](http://webmedia.oreck.com/optout.html)

## The Way We Use Information

We do not sell or rent personally-identifying information collected during your use of our Website without your permission.

We use non-personally-identifying information we collect at our site to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site’s content, layout, and services.

We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, new services and promotions. We may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience or requests, which we may use to customize our service for you.

We use your e-mail address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings and communications relevant to your use of the site. We will not send you promotions or announcements unless you give us permission to do so. You can opt out of receiving such contact by sending an email to [privacy@oreck.com](mailto:privacy@oreck.com).

If you place a request for products or services, we use your personal information to ship your order; if the products or services are from a retail partner, we may provide your relevant information to that retailer for purposes of the transaction. If you establish a credit account with us or our providers, we collect additional information, including billing information, credit card number and expiration date, and tracking information from checks or money orders.

We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.

During the normal course of doing business, we will continue to share your information among our business units, our affiliates and unaffiliated third parties as necessary. If you obtain goods or services provided by one of our retail partners or service providers, we may exchange with the vendor personally-identified information about you for purposes of your transaction.

At times, we need to share the e-mail addresses of those who have unsubscribed from our email list with our partners (list brokers, affiliates and broadcast email vendors) ONLY for the purpose of making sure that they too remove those email addresses from their lists. At times, we do share physical mailing addresses with reputable, trusted catalog vendors who offer quality products we think might be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your physical mailing address with other companies, please let us know by sending an e-mail to privacy@oreck.com, and include your name and physical mailing address. You can also call us at 1-800-289-5888 or send regular mail to Oreck Direct LLC, Attn: Privacy, 565 Marriott Dr, Nashville TN 37214.

## Security

We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. When you place an order at Oreck.com, our secure server software (SSL) encrypts all the information you input before it is sent to us, including your name, address, phone number and credit card number. All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe. To update, correct or delete the information that we collect online you can contact send an email to privacy@oreck.com. Your account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in your not being able to access member services.

## Children Under 13

We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Website, and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided us with personally-identifying information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

## Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy became effective on August 18, 2011, any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our Website. If there are ever changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, and how we use it. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy.
